GOURAB DAS

Balarampur, Purulia, West Bengal

+91-9547110160

gouravdasrrr123@gmail.com

★3 CodeChef | ★ 3 HackerRank

in <u>Linkedin</u> 🖫 <u>Github</u>

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY:

I am looking for an opportunity that will help me to grow ahead in software field, want to learn industry level work and do live projects. I can learn anything very quickly with hard work, for last 6 years I was studying core domain but in very short time I switched myself to it domain.

TECHNICAL SKILL		PROFILE
Languages	C++ Java SQL HTML	<u>LeetCode</u> <u>CodeChef</u>
DataBase	MySql MongoDB	CodeForces
Frameworks	CSS BootStrap	HackerRank GeeksforGeeks

WORK EXPERIENCE

Accenture April 2022 - June 2022

Coding Virtual Experience

- Object Oriented Programming
- Refactoring Continuous
- Integration Agile Planning
- Agile Planning

July 2021 - February 2022 **Fusion BPO**

Associate Customer Service at Meesho

- Calling
- Email
- Chat Process

PROJECTS:

EMPLOYEE MANAGEMENT SYSTEM Link

JsonPowerDB is a Real-time, High Performance, Lightweight and Simple to Use, Rest API based Multi-mode DBMS. JsonPowerDB has ready to use API for Json document DB, RDBMS, Key-value DB, GeoSpatial DB and Time Series DB functionality. JPDB supports and advocates for true serverless and pluggable API development.

ChatBot with Portfolio Link

A chatbot is a computer program that simulates and processes human conversation, allowing humans to interact with digital devices as if they were communicating with a real person.

EDUCATION:

Bachelor of Technology in Mechanical Engineering

2019 - 2022

Maulana Abul Kalam Azad University of Technology, West Bengal, Kolkata 8.06 CGPA

Diploma in Mechanical Engineering

West Bengal State Council of Technical Education Burdwan

7.01 CGPA

2016 - 2019